Okay, so now we have a better understanding of the main activity.
现在我们能更好地理解 MainActivity 了
Remember that you can think of an activity as a single screener or app.
你可以将 Activity 想象成一个屏幕或应用
By lesson five, we'll find out that this isn't necessarily true.
在第 5 节课中 我们将发现这也不完全正确
But for now this simplification is fine.
但现在可以这么简单地理解
In most apps you've built this far, your app has had a single activity.
在你构建的大多数应用中 只有一个 Activity
Near the end of the Just Java app, you added code that sent an intent to
在 Just Java 应用快结束时 你添加了向电子邮件应用
an email app to send an email out with a coffee order summary.
发送 intent 的代码 目的是发送一封含有咖啡点单信息的电子邮件
And then the Miwok App will also be sending intents, but
Miwok 应用也会发送 intent
this time we're not launching into other apps on Android device.
但是这次我们不会进入 Android 设备中的其他应用中
Instead, we're sending intents to open other activities that are created
而是发送 intent 来打开我们在 Miwok 应用中
within our Miwok App.
创建的其他 Activity
So we should have five activities in our app, the main activity
因此应用中应该有五个 Activity 即 Main Activity
as well as an activity for each of the four categories of words.
以及四个单词类别对应的 Activity
When we click on a category in the main activity,
当我们点击 Main Activity 中的某个类别时
we'll send an intent to open a new activity.
我们将发送一个 intent 来打开新的 Activity
That will eventually contain a list of Miwok phrases for that category.
最终包含该类别的米沃克短语列表
To start off with, all activities will be empty.
一开始所有 Activity 都是空的
But this activity will eventually show the list of number words, and
但是这个 Activity 最终会显示一个数字单词列表
this activity will show the list of family member words and
这个 Activity 会显示家庭成员单词列表
etc., for colors and phrases.
还有颜色列表和短语列表
So let's work on creating these four other activities in our app.
我们来创建应用中的这四个其他 Activity
I'll walk you through how to create a new activity in Android Studio.
我将在 Android Studio 中逐步讲解如何创建新的 Activity
Right-click on the package in the project directory,
在项目目录下右击文件包
go to New &gt; Activity &gt; Empty Activity.
依次转到 New &gt; Activity &gt; Empty Activity
When the wizard pops up, give the activity a name.
系统弹出向导后 为该 Activity 设置一个名称
In this case, we will use NumbersActivity, and
这里我们将使用 NumbersActivity
accept the default and click Finish.
接受默认设置并点击完成
Now it's your turn to create activities for
现在请你为剩下的短语 颜色和家庭成员类别
the remaining categories, phrases, colors and family members.
创建 Activity
If you run the app on your device there should be no errors.
在设备上运行应用时 应该没有错误
However, you won't be able to click the category buttons to open these
但是 在下一步我们添加更多代码前
activities until we add more code in the next step.
你无法点击类别按钮并打开这些 Activity
After you create each new activity, navigate to the AndroidManifest.xml file
新建每个 Activity 后 依次转到 App &gt; Manifest 文件夹
under the App Manifest folder to observe how it's changed.
打开 AndroidManifest.xml 文件 看看有何变化
Now, to recap what your tasks are, first,
现在总结下你要完成的任务
I'd like you to create the four new activities in the Miwok app.
首先请在 Miwok 应用中创建四个新的 Activity
So that would be the phrase activity,
也就是 Phrase Activity
the numbers activity, the family activity and the colors activity.
Numbers Activity Family Activity 和 Colors Activity
And then next, go ahead and
然后
navigate to the AndroidManifest.xml file and then answer this question.
转到 AndroidManifest.xml 文件并回答下面这个问题
So how does the AndroidManifest.xml file
当你向应用中添加更多 Activity 时
change as you add more activities to the app?
AndroidManifest.xml 文件是如何变化的？
Now, I know this is a new file that you haven't seen before, but
我知道这是一个新文件 你之前没有见过
try to make an educated guess by checking out the visual changes
但是请根据你在该文件中观察到的外观变化
that you see in that file, and go ahead and write your answers here.
试着猜测一下答案 并将答案写在这里